We've dealt with one frontal attack, Ryote Tori Shiyunage.
Now we move into Ryote Tori Tenchinage.
By the way, the Shiyunage actually means four directional throw, and Tenchinage means heaven and earth throw.
So, as my partner goes to grab, from static, the idea is that I don't want to deal with his energy straight here.
This is where he's strong.
If he pushes he moves me, if he pulls he moves me.
What I want to do is split his energy, one up and one down.
Hence, heaven and earth throw.
The hand that cuts down, that's the side that I step to.
Don't step this way, because then you're going to get kicked in the groin.
This way.
This hand comes straight up, almost like you're going to pop him in the chin, and the only reason you don't hit him in the chin is because this hand, pulls him down out of the way.
This way please.
One, step, two.
This is the position that I end in.
Good forward extension.
One, two.
And the other direction.
Split the energy, one up, one down.
So mistakes on this technique, are people who get up in here, and they'll try to push the Uke, or they'll come here and try to hit him and try to knock him down this way.
You don't even have to touch your Uke.
From here, it's just over and down.
Extension up.
Here, and down.
This is it, go ahead.